funky-buddha.com 2019-01-26

# Privacy Policy

Personal data shall mean any information or combination of information that could identify you directly (e.g. Full Name) or indirectly (e.g., by pseudonymous data such as Social Insurance Registry Number (AMKA) or ID card Number). This means that personal data include information like e-mail address, home address, mobile phone number, personal preferences, social welfare information.

By providing this privacy policy, you agree to the collection, processing and use of personal data by the Company, in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and the following terms of use:

CONTROLLER

Controller shall mean the natural person or legal entity, or a public authority, or a service, or any other entity that individually or jointly with others determines the purposes, conditions and manner of processing personal data. For the purposes of this privacy policy, the controller is: ALTEX S.A.

You may contact the controller of your personal data at the following e-mail address: eshop@funky-buddha.com, if you do not agree to the collection, processing or use of your personal data by the Company, in accordance with the applicable law and the present privacy policy of the Company. In this case, the service may no longer be available

PERSONAL DATA COLLECTED DURING YOUR BROWSING ON THE WEBSITE

If you visit the Company's website without subscribing or ordering as a visitor, the following data are collected in order for the Company to be informed about the visit to the site and which are the minimum in order to comply with the Data Processing Authority that requires their minimal processing:

Device data: device ID, operating systems, device version or other identifiers

Connection details: time, date, visit’s duration, user's place of origin, IP address, and other login details

PERSONAL DATA COLLECTED DURING SIGNING UP AND ACCOUNT MANAGING 

If you choose to become a member and create a user account, you are asked for personal data, such as your email address, to which you will receive our newsletters, if you consent.

If you choose to place an order on our products then you will need to enter additional personal information to complete the transaction. Compulsory details for each transaction are your full name, a fixed telephone number, your address (street, city, postal code), a shipping address and the type of receipt you prefer (receipt, invoice). Optional details are the mobile phone number (in case we need to contact you directly to finalize your order when you have saved your shopping cart, to inform you about the availability of products, etc.) and occupation.

The data categories are access data, account details, contact information, logins data, device data, ordering details and are requested to complete the order, as well as to ensure the security of our applications and transactions in them, in order to fulfill the obligation of delivering the order.

In order to align our Company’s interests with your interests, we have created relevant control mechanisms. We will only process your personal data based on the legitimate interests of the Company only if we believe that we can protect them against any risk. They will never be transferred to third unauthorized parties, and if any item is transferred to an affiliate company, it shall be controlled and must comply with our Privacy Policy and also demonstrate the security level it provides with sufficient data.

RETENTION OF PERSONAL DATA

We keep your personal data for as long as we need them and for the purpose for which we maintain them in order to meet your needs or to comply with our legal obligations.

To determine how long your personal data are retained, we use the following criteria:

In case you buy products we maintain them throughout our contractual relationship. When you participate in a promotional offer we maintain it throughout the offer.

When you contact us to submit a question we keep them for as long as we need to process your question.

When you create an account we keep them until we are asked to delete them or after a period of inactivity determined in accordance with local regulations and guidelines.

When you grant your consent to marketing notifications, we retain your personal information until you either remove your registration or request it to be deleted, or after a period of inactivity determined in accordance with local regulations and guidelines.

We may retain some of your personal data to comply with our legal or regulatory obligations and to be in a position to manage our rights (claims before the Courts) or for statistical purposes. When we no longer need to use your personal data, we will delete them from our systems and records or make them anonymous so that you can no longer be identified by them.

COUNTRIES OF PERSONAL DATA PROCESSING

We process data mainly within the European Union (EU) (and within the European Economic Area (EEA)). Irrespective of whether the EEA provider is located within the EU / EEA, he is required to sign a data processing agreement with us, if he complies with the criteria of Article 44 et seq. of the GDPR.

However, some of the service providers we work with are located outside the EU and EEA. All data recipients outside European countries are first assessed for the level of protection they offer and only if they can demonstrate an adequate level of protection are chosen as service providers.

INFORMATION ABOUT COOKIES

Cookies are small text files stored on the device used to browse our site in order to make your visit operational and appealing. Some of them are deleted after the expiry of the browser session (session cookies).

Others remain on the device and allow the Company to identify the browser on the next visit (persistent cookies). You have the option to set up your browser in order that you learn how to set cookies and decide whether to accept or reject them in specific cases or in general. If you do not accept the installation of cookies, the functionality of the website or application may be reduced.

COOKIES CATEGORIES

FUNCTIONAL COOKIES:

They allow the storage of information that has already been submitted and improve the user's ability to enjoy personalized browsing. They collect anonymized information and do not allow tracking of the site's browsing.

PERFORMANCE COOKIES:

They collect information about the use of a webpage / application and do not store information that allows the user to be identified. Any information stored is used solely to improve and implement the website's performance and therefore the experience provided to the user.

COOKIES FOR PURPOSES OF PROMOTION OF PRODUCTS:

They are used to provide targeted advertising relevant and tailored to his interests. They are also used to limit the frequency of an advertisement and measure the effectiveness of the advertising campaign. They mainly record if you have visited the website or not. This information may be shared with third parties to improve targeted advertising.

PRIVACY OF TRANSACTIONS 

Our compliance with the privacy of transactions is considered self-evident.

The two main principles of the traditional transactions concern as well the case of e-commerce.

All the information transferred by the user / member of ALTEX S.A. are confidential and the ALTEX S.A. company has taken all the substantial measures in order to use them when necessary in the framework of services provided.

ALTEX S.A. never reveals the data of its customers and its transactions, with the exemption of written authorization on your behalf or court’s judgment or decision of any relevant public authority.

In the case where ALTEX S.A. cooperates with third parties to support its systems, it secures the confidentiality of data.

You can ask any data kept for you as well as their correction, in case where you can substantiate the existence of errors.

For your own safety, you shall handle all the confidential and undisclosed information provided through our service and you shall not reveal them to third parties.

TRANSACTION SECURITY

ALTEX S.A. recognizes the importance of personal data and transaction security and takes all the necessary measures by implementing the most modern and technologically advanced methods in order to ensure the greatest possible security.

 All the relevant information about your personal data and transactions are secure and undisclosed.

The security of the SFP S.A. online shop is achieved through the following procedure: User’s identification

As regards your identification, your email and your secret personal code of security (password) are used in order to give you access in complete safety to your personal data, whenever you are registered. You have the possibility to change your secret personal code of security (password) and the address of your electronic mail (e-mail) as many times as you wish.

The only person who has access to these data is you through the above-mentioned codes and you are solely responsible for the absolute secrecy and concealment of your data by third parties. In case of a loss or a leak, you must proceed in our immediate notification, or otherwise the SFP S.A. online shop is not responsible for the use of the secret code by unauthorized persons.

For safety reasons, we recommend you to change regularly your password and to avoid the use of similar and easily detected codes (for example, date of birth). Moreover, we recommend you to use not only letters and numbers, but also symbols and password creation.

Payment

The payment by credit card or PayPal is an absolutely secure payment method for our customers.

ALTEX S.A. shall never become aware of any information of your card or account. As regards the order’s payment, the company automatically redirects you to the Eurobank’s website or PayPal website without coming into contact in any case with the information and data of your credit/debit card.

This information is transferred to EUROBANK or PayPal system by using an encrypted connection and through the secure transaction systems. 

RIGHT TO MODIFY THE PRESENT POLICY AND FINAL PROVISIONS.

The Company reserves the right to modify this personal data protection policy in order to comply with any legal or regulatory obligations. For each major change there will be the corresponding update.

The Company shall take all the necessary technical and organizational measures to protect the important data of yours. The less information you provide, the less control you have.

In case you wish to browse anonymously and do not wish the behavior during the browsing to be evaluated by our Company and our certified partners, you must properly configure your browser.
